

mhatreankita275@gmail.com

8108069395

0

Navi Mumbai, India

in linkedin.com/in/ankitamhatre275

8

mhatreankita275@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages - C# , Java, HTML and CSS, JavaScript , Bootstrap,QT-QML

Database -MS SQL Server- 2012, Oracle

Technologies- ASP.Net MVC, WCF

Tools used- Visual studio, ArcGIS Qt-Creator, SQL Server Management Studio

LANGUAGES

English Marathi Hindi

Ankita Mhatre

SoftwareDeveloper

Having total 3.7years of experience in software development and design using ASP. Net MVC. Served as an effective and motivated team lead. Strong working ability in agile environments. Worked on technologies such as MVC, WCF, Html, CSS, JavaScript Bootstrap, SQL, Java etc. Ready to learn new technologies and give my 100% towards the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE-

Software Engineer

Bigiota Analytics

04/2023- present

Task

- Coordinated with other engineers to evaluate and improve software.
- Fixing Bugs in existing software using Asp.net MVC, html, javascript.
- Created website UI using bootstrap.
- Created UI for Agent-GPT Application and Travel Itinerary Application.
- Prepared project Documentation.

Software Engineer

Ixia Solutions LLP

05/2022-04/2023

Task

- Coordinated with other engineers to evaluate and improve software.
- Fixing Bugs in existing software using Asp.net MVC, html, javascript.
- Worked with software development and testing team members to design and develop robust solutions to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability, and performance.
- Worked as Team Lead.
- Strong working ability in agile environments.

Developer Trainee

CyberTech System and Software Ltd.

01/2020-05/2022,

Tasks

- Created website UI using bootstrap.
- Worked on project Skill Matrix Application using **Asp.net MVC**, **html**.
- Development of software using QT QML framework and ArcGIS Qt-Creator.
- Writing test cases for initial development testing. Performing unit testing and preparing project documentation.
- Collaborated on high priority projects with tact and a strong attention to detail.
- Fixed bugs in existing software and implemented enhancements and Improved functionality.
- Project development, performing unit testing.
- Handling database operation like creating tables, stored procedure etc.
- Worked on different projects in ASP.Net MVC, WCF Technology like Geo-Civic Property Tax, Expense Portal Application, and SBCUSDCovid Application.
- Worked on project using ArcGIS Qt-Creator and language as QT-QML.

PERSONAL PROJECTS-

Medical Agency Management System (MCA Project)

- Platform/Technology used JAVA Net Beans.
- **Description** -System designed to automate the task of medical shops where information about medicines, expenses, inventory, etc.to make the process easy.
- Year: MCA

EDUCATION-

MBA-IT (Pursuing)

Welingkar Institute of Management Studies, Mumbai 2021-2023,

MCA (Masters of Computer Application)

University of Mumbai

2019 - 2020, 70% **/** 7.74cgpa

B.Sc.IT

University of Mumbai

2015 - 2016, 67.25%

CERTIFICATES COURSES-

- Certificate Course for Oracle 11g from Seed InfoTech. 2016-2017
- Certificate Course for JAVA from Seed InfoTech

Declaration:

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

2016-2017

Date:

Place: Nerul, Navi Mumbai. (Ankita Shekhar Mhatre)